原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
翻译     小郭郭  kathy567  glida  TracyOY
翻译     海云生  Carolgcz  苏葵
校对     elingbow
时间轴   西·查  知之  啾啾啾  壬虚浪影
后期     渔夫
总监     吃冰棒
Haunted Heart - Christina Aguilera
♪ There's no bell when you call for me ♪
♪ You'll be falling for miles ♪
晚上八点
♪ I'm bewitched by your misery ♪
♪ But I love it when you smile ♪
♪ Let me know what you want from me ♪
♪ Whisper "love" in my ears ♪
♪ Before you try to get your hooks in me ♪
妈妈
♪ I should warn you, my dear ♪
♪ My heart is a haunted house ♪
♪ Once you're in, you ain't getting out ♪
爸爸
♪ It's the trap you've been waiting for ♪
♪ Ain't no windows, ain't no doors ♪
♪ No escaping the way you feel ♪
♪ It's like a dream, but you hope it's real ♪
♪ My, my, my heart ♪
♪ M-m-m-my heart is a haunted haunted house ♪
♪ M-m-m-my heart is a haunted ♪
♪ Haunted house ♪
亲爱的
My love.
Cara mia.
戒指  戒指  不  不  不  不
The ring! The ring! Oh, no! No, no, no!
东西  最好的手总戴着戒指
Oh, Thing! Best hand always has the ring!
亲爱的讨人嫌们
Dearly be-loathed,
很荣幸看到我们的家族
it is indeed a rare privilege to see our family
为了亚当斯家的传统齐聚一堂
gathered together for this Addams tradition.
我们在此举行婚礼
To commence this ceremony
目送这两位
and deliver these two
走入无聊的婚姻
into the yawning void of matrimony,
下面把青柠放入椰子  一起喝掉
we put the lime in the coconut and drink them both up.
现在我宣布你们...
I now pronounce you...
怪物  怪胎
Monsters! freaks!
滚出去  亚当斯家的
Get out, Addams!
你们在这里住得够久的了
You've been here long enough!
我们忍你们很久了
We've had enough of your kind!
亚当斯一族不属于这里
Addams aren't wanted here!
滚出去
Leave already!
现在我宣布你们结为夫妻
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
快点  把青柠放进椰子里
Quick, put the lime in the coconut
然后喝掉
and drink 'em both up!
对不起  我情不自禁
Sorry, I couldn't help myself.
这里是我们的家
This is our home!
-你们不属于这里  -快滚
- You're not wanted! - We don't want you here!
所有人  从桥上走
Everyone, to the bridge!
开火
Fire!
你们一对小情侣快离开这里
You two love bats better fly out of here!
我搞定他们
I'll hold them off!
玛祖卡
Mazurka!
抓住我的大衣毛领
Grab onto my hairy hump!
我能从这里看到我的房子
I think I can see my house from here.
不对  那是女子监狱
Oh, no. That's a women's prison.
戈麦斯  为什么无论我们走到哪里
Oh, Gomez, why do hordes of angry villagers
都躲不开那些愤怒的村民
follow us everywhere we go?
我们现在安全了  亲爱的  这是最重要的
We are safe, my love, that is all that matters.
我想找一个新家
I want to find a new home
远离尘世
that is shrouded from the world.
某个真正属于我们的地方
Someplace that is truly us.
没错  一个可怕的地方  腐烂的地方
Yes! Somewhere horrible! Somewhere corrupt!
任何心智正常的人
Somewhere that no one in their right mind
都不会踏足的地方
would be caught dead in!
欢迎来到新泽西州
看什么看
不开心吗  亲爱的
Unhappy, darling?
是的  非常不开心
Yes, completely.
戈麦斯  你摧毁了我的心墙
Oh, Gomez, you have torn down my walls
把你的名字捅进我的心脏
and stabbed your name onto my heart.
我苍白的爱人
My wan temptress,
你的手冷得像一条死鱼
your hand is as cold as a dead fish.
亲爱的  那就是一条死鱼
My love, that is a dead fish.
的确如此
So it is.
亲爱的
Darling,
你死气沉沉的眉间是有一条皱纹吗
is that a wrinkle I see on your pallid brow?
怎么了
What's wrong?
我们不能永远逃跑  亲爱的
We can't run forever, my love.
我想再次拥有自己的家
I want a home again.
我想让孩子们在和平中长大
I want our children to grow up in peace.
我想挑选墓地
I want to pick out cemetery plots.
莫蒂西亚  我用生命发誓
Morticia, I swear on my life
我会找到新家的
I will find us a new home.
你会实现所有的愿望
And your every wish shall be granted.
我的爱人
Mon amour.
法语  你知道这对我来说意味什么
French. You know what that does to me.
♪ 野东西 ♪
♪ Wild thing ♪
♪ 你让我的心 ♪
♪ You make my heart... ♪
我们撞上东西了
We hit something!
他还好吗
Is he all right?
不  他看起来完全精神错乱了
No, he seems perfectly demented.
"州立精神病罪犯医院"
"State Hospital for the Criminally Insane."
戈麦斯
Gomez.
那里一定就是精神病院了
That must be the asylum.
感谢神灵
Oh, thank goodness.
一个可以过夜的好地方
A decent place to sleep for the night.
谢谢  老家伙  带路
Thank you, old boy. Lead the way.
精神病院
这里很安静  太安静了
It's quiet. Too quiet.
这里一定正值淡季
Must be the off-season.
有人吗
Hello?
一个人也没有
There's no one here.
是不是被遗弃了
Could it be abandoned?
这里诡异  怪僻
It's creepy. Kooky.
神秘  恐怖
Mysterious. Spooky.
出去
Get out!
这里真可怕
It's hideous.
这里真糟糕
It's horrible.
这里是我们的家
It's home.
亚当斯一家
十三年后
多么美好的早晨
What a lovely morning!
想得美
Nice try.
出去
Get out!
你在喝早餐咖啡前总是这么暴躁
Oh, you're always so grumpy before your morning coffee.
好些了吗
Better?
《小妇人》
莫蒂西亚
勒奇
Lurch,
该吃早餐了
it's time for breakfast.
东西
Thing.
让伊卡博德叫孩子们起床
Have Ichabod wake the children.
勒奇  可以请你为房子加尘吗
Lurch, would you mind dusting the house?
慢点  克娄巴特拉
Slowly, Cleopatra.
我可不想让我最爱的非洲食人花噎到
I wouldn't want my favorite African Strangler to choke.
好啦  伊卡博德  我醒了
All right, Ichabod. I'm awake.
不会太久
Not for long.
真成熟  帕格斯利
Real mature, Pugsley.
得了
Oh, please.
你在我的年龄没有玩过斧子吗
You never threw an axe when you were my age?
当然玩过  我百发百中
Of course I did. I never missed.
多希望有个人给这乏味的生活加点料
How I wish something would liven up this already tedious day.
你尽力了  伊卡博德
Thanks for trying, Ichabod.
帕格斯利
Pugsley?
帕格斯利  该练剑了
Pugsley! It's time for sword practice.
帕格斯利
Pugsley!
游戏开始
Let the games begin.
帕格斯利来了
Here's Pugsley!
好了  儿子  够了
All right, son. That's enough.
最近他们爆炸的速度真快
They blow up so fast these days.
别逼我上去抓你
Don't make me come up there!
最后警告你一次
This is your last warning!
我的头
My head.
帕格斯利  我们本该练剑术的
Pugsley, we're supposed to be working on your swordplay.
你的马刀玛祖卡舞仪式就在两周后
Your Sabre Mazurka is two weeks away,
而你几乎没有练习过
and you've barely practiced at all.
我少练了一次而已  有什么大不了
So I missed one practice. What's the big deal?
大不了
The big deal?
马刀玛祖卡舞仪式是年轻人生命中
The Sabre Mazurka is the most important day
最重要的一天
in a young man's life.
是成为亚当斯族人的标志
It's what makes you an Addams.
那一天  你的整个家族将围绕着你
It's the day your entire family gathers around you
判定你身为人的价值
and passes judgment on your worth as a human being.
听说和感恩节很像
I hear it's like Thanksgiving.
但舞剑太过时了
But swords are so old-fashioned.
我喜欢爆破
I'm more of a demolitions man.
玛祖卡舞中没有炸药的位置
Explosives have no place in a Mazurka.
交出来
Hand them over.
全部
All of them.
还有三硝基甲苯
And the TNT.
还有M-80炸药
And the M-80s.
烟火筒  摔炮  手榴弹
Roman candles. Bang snaps. Holy Hand Grenades.
儿子
Son,
我们家族已经有十三年没有齐聚一堂了
our family hasn't been all together in 13 years.
他们从世界各地到这里
They are coming from all over the world
见证你的大日子
to see you on your special day.
我只是希望一切顺利
I just want it to go perfectly.
好吧  老爸  我练剑
All right, Pop. I'll practice.
这才是我儿子
That's my boy.
腐败
Putrid.
令人震惊
Horrifying.
脾是我的
I call spleen.
星期三
Wednesday.
请不要把墨点留在桌子上
Please, no ink stains on the table.
好的  母亲
Yes, Mother.
戈麦斯  收到玛祖卡舞仪式邀请函的人
Gomez, everyone we've invited
都威胁我们要来出席
to the Mazurka has threatened to come.
我就知道  是不是很棒
I know. Isn't it wonderful?
亚当斯家族成员齐聚一堂
All Addamses under one roof again.
是的  但是他们睡在哪里
Yes, but where will everyone sleep?
我们让勒奇修整墓地了
We'll have Lurch fix up the mausoleum.
可以把那里当成露营地
It'll be like sleepaway camp.
很好  亲爱的
Very well, darling.
费斯特叔叔
Uncle Fester!
兄弟
Brother!
别担心  我没事
Don't worry, I'm okay.
平板玻璃阻碍了我的坠落路线
The plate glass window broke my fall.
堆起来  折磨  冲他们吼
Rick'em, rack'em, roar'em, buzz
亚当斯就做亚当斯的事
Addams is as Addams does
你能来我好激动
I am thrilled you're here!
我没有迟到吧
I'm not late, am I?
其实  仪式两周后才会举行
Actually, we weren't expecting you for another two weeks.
所以我没有迟到
So, not late.
我向你道歉  亲爱的
I apologize, darling.
是我请费斯特早点来
You see, I asked Fester to come early
帮助帕格斯利练习玛祖卡舞的
to help Pugsley with his Mazurka practice.
不  不
No! No!
坏猫咪  坏猫咪
Bad Kitty! That's a bad Kitty!
要是我知道你会提前到达
If I'd known you were coming,
就为你准备好地牢了
I would have prepared the dungeon.
请别担心  我可以睡阁楼
Please, don't worry. I'll sleep in the attic.
你甚至感觉不到我在这里
You won't even know I'm here.
我练这个很多次了  住过不少人家
I've practiced that move in a lot of people's homes.
叔叔  你可以给我们讲讲门外的世界吗
Uncle, can you tell us what's beyond the gate?
你怎么想问这个问题  宝贝
Why ever would you ask that, dear?
今天早上雾中传来奇怪的声音
I heard a strange noise in the fog earlier,
我想去调查一下
and I should like to investigate.
外面什么都没有  只有无聊的沼泽
There's nothing out there but boring marshland.
一定有什么的  我们从不出门
There must be something. We never go anywhere.
谁知道我们错过了多少未知的恐怖
Who knows the untold horrors we're missing out on.
亲爱的  我们需要的恐怖都在这里了
Darling, we have all the horror we need, right here.
费斯特叔叔想去哪都可以
Uncle Fester can go wherever he likes.
不  不  还是有些限制的
Now, now, there are some restrictions.
我不能去商场
You know, I can't go to the mall,
动物园  或者是...
or a zoo, or a building...
等你长大了
When you're older,
就可以随心所欲去旅行了
you can travel to your heart's content.
但现在  你待在这里更安全
But for now, it's safer for you here.
苏格拉底  走
Socrates, come.
...南美洲  欧洲  中国
...South America, Europe, China,
亚洲  非洲的大部分地方
Asia, most parts of Africa.
我可以去南极洲
I'm allowed in Antarctica!
您正在收看的是《家  艺术与园艺》节目
You're watching Home, Art and Garden television.
世界如此之大  无数可怜人
The world's a big place, full of poor souls
不懂搭接接头是什么东西
who don't know the difference between shiplap and Shinola.
让我来帮助你们
Well, I'm here to help.
我会将你们毫无创意的家
I take your uninspired living space
变成你们梦想中的完美宫殿
and turn it into the perfect palace of your dreams.
无论你家的设计有多老土  我都能帮你
No matter how outdated your design sense, I can help you.
我唯一的缺点
My only flaw?
就是过分关心
Sometimes I care too much.
我是玛尔戈·尼德勒
I'm Margaux Needler,
为您带来《设计干预》
and I'm about to stage a Design Intervention!
《玛尔戈设计干预》
提前说一声不客气
You're welcome in advance.
今天  我们将对目前为止最大的项目
Today, we're putting the finishing touches
进行收尾
on our biggest project yet.
同化镇
Assimilation.
我们不仅是改造一所房子
We didn't just make over a house.
欢迎来到同化镇
我们改造了一整个小镇
We made over a whole town!
两周后  在我们的季终直播集中
And in just two weeks, on our live season finale,
您可以在同化镇买下自己的房子
you will be able to buy your very own piece of Assimilation.
没错
That's right!
这是《设计干预》首次
In a Design Intervention first,
出售整个社区
we are putting a whole neighborhood up for sale.
您将有机会购买梦想小镇上的
This will be your chance to purchase the house of your dreams
梦想之家
in the town of your dreams!
心动吗  我看是的
Sounds good? I thought so.
欢迎来到同化镇  邻居
Welcome to Assimilation, neighbor.
欢迎来到同化镇
本节目由"邻居之窥"为您播出
This program brought to you by Neighborhood Peeps.
您的邻居在看您
Your neighbors are watching!
好的  结束
And, we're out!
很棒  完美
Love it. Perfect.
准备彩排
Let's set up for the walk-through.
玛尔戈  你感觉可以吗
Margaux, did that feel good to you?
不可以  格伦
No, Glenn.
还需要更多气球和五彩纸屑
We need more balloons, more confetti.
-收到  -我们卖的是什么
- Roger that. - What are we selling here?
美梦  知道美梦是怎么产生的吗
Big dreams. You know how you get big dreams?
高收视率
With big ratings.
-明白  -气球加倍
- Got it. - Double the balloons.
我还要一场五彩纸屑暴风雪
And I want a blizzard of confetti.
暴风雪要足够大
I want so much confetti that we need
大到需要出动雪警去找孩子
snow patrols to find lost children.
我把我的家庭改造帝国都赌在这个小镇上了
I bet my home improvement empire on this town.
所有房子都要卖出去  否则我们就要失业了
Every house must sell or we're out of business!
-必须要完美  -妈妈
- It's got to be perfect! - Mom!
你绝对不会相信
You're never gonna believe this.
什么  派克
What is it, Parker?
我在山上发现了一所诡异的豪宅
I found a creepy mansion up on the hill!
我很欣慰你出去探险了  派克
I'm so glad you're exploring, Parker,
但我现在没时间闲聊  亲爱的
but I don't have time to talk right now, sweetheart.
妈妈需要去帮助他人
Mama needs to help people.
我需要帮助  我就不是他人吗
I need help. Aren't I people?
你真可爱
Oh, you're cute.
你下午不是要去薯条店打工吗
Don't you have Chipper 'N' Cheer practice this afternoon?
去吧  宝贝
Run along, honey.
格伦  收视率预期是多少
Now, Glenn, what are the numbers we're expecting?
-你看这里...  -妈妈
- Well, if you look here... - Mom!
左边一点  上去一点
Left a bit. Up a bit.
下去一点
Now, down a bit.
完美
Perfect.
三  二  一
And three, two, one...
你害我没射中
You made me miss!
你知道我蓄力了多久吗
Do you know how long it took for me to set this up?
听我说  帕格斯利
Look, Pugsley...
你就要表演玛祖卡舞了  而你还没准备好
Your Mazurka's coming up, and, well, you're not ready.
即使只有我注意到了这一点
Even if I am the only one who sees it.
注意听
So, pay attention,
说不定你可以蒙混过关
and you might actually get through this.
等等
Wait.
你要帮我
You're going to help me?
为什么
Why?
因为你是我弟弟
Because you are my brother.
我爱你
And... I love you.
好吧  你打算怎么帮我
All right. How are you gonna help me?
看到那边那个洞了吗
You see that hole over there?
站到它旁边去
Go stand beside it.
那个洞吗
That hole?
那个洞
That hole.
我不明白
I don't get it.
亲爱的  不是我挑剔
Darling, not to criticize,
但你已经尽力压紧了吗
but is that really as tight as you can make it?
抱歉  戈麦斯
I'm sorry, Gomez.
我只是因为准备玛祖卡舞有点分心
I'm just a bit preoccupied with the Mazurka preparations.
我也是
Oh, I am as well!
我怕帕格斯利过于自信
I fear Pugsley is overconfident
不能真正明白
and doesn't truly understand
这项传统的重要性
the importance of this tradition.
好消息  帕格斯利不见了
Good news, everybody. Pugsley's gone.
星期三  我知道你的把戏
Wednesday, I know that tone of voice.
把你弟弟挖出来  马上去
Dig up your brother. At once.
基因库都被你们削弱了
You're weakening the gene pool.
等等
Hold on.
你手里拿着什么
What do you have there?
我不确定  我喜欢这个
I'm not sure. I like it.
非常...怎么说  伤心的反义词
It's so... What's the word? The opposite of sad?
亲爱的  把它给我
Darling, bring that to me.
奇怪  通常这东西的另一端
Strange, there's usually a murderous clown
应该系着一个凶残的小丑
attached to the other end of these.
星期三  别动
Wednesday, don't move!
我的天  这到底是什么
What, in the name of all that is unholy, is that?
味道像棉花糖
It tastes like cotton candy.
你怎么知道棉花糖的味道
How do you know what cotton candy tastes like?
蒂西  那是我年轻时犯的错
Tish, it was my youth. I made mistakes.
星期三  这粉色的东西是哪来的
Wednesday, wherever did this pink thing come from?
外面
Outside.
到处都是
They're everywhere.
我从没见过这么奇怪的天气
Strangest weather system I've ever seen.
这是什么  哪来的
What is that? Where's it coming from?
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait.
雾升起来了
The fog, it's lifting.
这种情况只可能是因为...
Well, that would only happen if...
有人把沼泽排空了  是谁呢
Someone drained the marsh. But who?
一座小镇  这可不妙
A town. This is not good.
我们必须马上下去
We must go down there
介绍我们自己
and introduce ourselves at once.
今天真是混乱得令人高兴
This day is becoming most wonderfully disruptive.
我们继续彩排  好吗
Let's keep going with the run-through, okay?
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
我非常高兴带你们参观我家
I'm so delighted to show you my house.
你们也可以拥有这样的家  只是没这么大
You can own one just like it, just less large.
之类之类的  灯台  吊顶
Blah, blah, blah. Sconces, crown molding.
接着我们就来到了重要的客厅
Which leads us to what I call the Salon de Grandé.
穿过这里  转弯  然后说
Cross here, turn, and then say something like,
"在我向你们展示风景之前
"Now, before I show you this view,
先去古董商店
go to an antique store,
买一把椅子  重装椅面
buy a chair, and reupholster it.
因为这美景需要坐下来欣赏"
'Cause you're gonna wanna sit down for this."
怎么了  怎么回事
What? What's the matter?
拜托  到底怎么了
For heaven's sake, what's going on?
我的牙上有东西吗  到底怎么了
Do I have something in my teeth? What is it?
都没有带滴水兽的房子
Not a single gargoyle.
或许这也不算是坏事
Maybe this isn't such a bad thing.
我们已经与世隔绝了好久
We have been isolated here for a while.
我可以预料到自己死于这里
I could really see myself dying here.
乖点  基蒂
Play nice, Kitty.
没人拿着火把和叉子
Well, no one is running at us
追我们  这是一个加分点
with torches and pitchforks, so that's a plus.
亲爱的  我们应该不用
You know, darling, I don't think we'll need
安排家人去陵墓了
to put the family in the mausoleum.
他们可以住在这里
They can stay here!
那他们绝对会不自在
The family would never be comfortable.
这里要过好多年
It will be years
才会腐败和衰落
before rust and decay set in.
你好
How you doing?
一切都...不一样
It's all so... different.
帕格斯利  别都喝光了
Pugsley, don't drink it all.
这位先生也想喝点
This gentleman wants some, too.
先生  没关系的
Sir, it's all right.
他已经喝完了
He's had all his shots!
这人真是神经兮兮
What a nervous man.
走吧  蒂西  我们去附近转转
Come on, Tish, let's explore the neighborhood.
我去逛两分钟
I'm gonna pop in here for two minutes
我们镇广场再见  好吗
and I'll meet you in the town square. Agreed?
很好  亲爱的
Very well, darling.
大家好啊
Good day, all.
我可不想打扰你们喝咖啡
Don't let me interrupt your cup of joe
或者什么别的
or whoever you have in there.
有什么像我一样黑暗苦涩的选择吗
So, what's dark and bitter here other than yours truly?
我们有马达加斯加翡翠圆豆
We have the Madagascar Emerald Peaberry,
夏季广藿烘焙
in a summer patchouli roast.
有橡木  樱桃与瑜伽风味
It has notes of oak, cherry, and yoga.
我想要点风味浓烈的
Hmm. You know, I'm looking for something a bit stronger.
给我试试那个吧
Ah! Let me try that.
莫蒂西亚  来尝尝这些咖啡渣
Mmm! Morticia, you have to try these coffee grounds.
颗粒感真的很棒
They have a wonderful grit!
等等  什么声音
Just a moment, what am I hearing?
♪ 这是我们的家园 ♪
♪ This is where we all belong, yeah ♪
♪ 大家一起来 ♪
♪ Everybody come together ♪
♪ 唱我们的歌  唱我们的歌 ♪
♪ Sing our song, sing our song ♪
♪ 生活很美好  我们是一个大家庭 ♪
♪ Life is really perfect We are one big family, yeah ♪
♪ 当你我变得相似时 ♪
♪ Everything is so much better ♪
♪ 一切都变得更好 ♪
♪ When I'm like you and you're like me ♪
♪ 当你可以泯然众人 ♪
♪ What's so great about being yourself
♪ 又何必做你自己 ♪
♪ When you can be like everyone else? ♪
真是太可怕了
Wow, that is absolutely horrible!
♪ 别无选择时  快乐很容易 ♪
♪ It's easy to be happy when you have no choice ♪
♪ 对  别无选择时  快乐很容易 ♪
♪ Yes, it's easy to be happy when you have no choice ♪
等等  我没猜错的话
Hold on, unless I miss my guess here,
这应该是音乐
I believe that is supposed to be music.
他们在唱一首传统歌曲
They're greeting us with
来欢迎我们
one of their traditional songs.
那我们也应该回敬一首
Well, then, we ought to do the same.
好主意  费斯特
Wonderful idea, Fester.
♪ 我们都在一起  是不是很棒 ♪
♪ Isn't it great when we are all together? ♪
♪ 再说一遍  直到你相信 ♪
♪ Say it again until you believe it ♪
♪ 我相信 ♪
♪ I believe it ♪
♪ 我们相信 ♪
♪ We believe it ♪
♪ 我愿向你们脱帽致敬 ♪
♪ I'd tip my hat to you ♪
♪ 我真的愿意 ♪
♪ I'd do just that ♪
♪ 直接脱帽为你们致敬 ♪
♪ Take it right off for you ♪
♪ 但我没有帽子 ♪
♪ But I haven't got a hat ♪
♪ 我只是个大学生  即使那样 ♪
♪ I'm just a college boy, even at that ♪
♪ 我愿向你们脱帽致敬 ♪
♪ I'd tip my hat to you ♪
♪ 但我没有帽子 ♪
♪ But I haven't got a hat ♪
怎么  我做了什么
What? What'd I do?
真无礼
How rude.
戈麦斯  我们应该回家
Gomez, we should return home.
莫蒂西亚  这里不是原来那个乡下
Morticia, this is not the old country.
没错  这些人有点不一样
True, these people are a little different.
但内心深处我们都一样
But deep down, we're all the same.
我们必须给他们机会  了解他们
We have to give them a chance. Get to know them.
我们得赢得他们的欢迎
We have to win them over.
"赢得他们的欢迎"
"Win them over"?
早上好  邻居
Well, good morning, neighbor!
玛尔戈·尼德勒
Margaux Needler.
戈麦斯·亚当斯  为你效劳
Gomez Addams. At your service.
这是我妻子莫蒂西亚
My wife, Morticia.
很荣幸
Charmed.
我们的孩子星期三和帕格斯利
Our children, Wednesday, Pugsley.
还有我兄弟费斯特
And my brother, Fester.
邻居好
Hey, neighbor!
知道吗  我们可以看到你的房间
You know, we can see right into your windows?
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
作为你们的邻居  我想给你们
As your neighbor, I'd like to offer you
一个千载难逢的机会
the opportunity of a lifetime.
你们想要世界知名室内设计师
How'd you like a free home makeover
给你们的家免费大改造吗
from a world-renowned interior designer?
这确实有点难度
It will be a challenge,
但我能快速翻新你们的旧房子
but I can beautify that old house of yours so fast,
快得让你们晕头转向
it'll make your head spin.
不想吹牛
I don't wanna brag,
但我的头已经会转了  瞧
but mine already does that. Look.
我想看看这个整容女能提供什么
I should like to see what this plastic woman has to offer.
好吧  什么时候方便拜访
Yes, well... When is a good time to stop by?
事实上  尼德勒女士
Actually, Ms. Needler...
亲爱的
Darling...
随时欢迎
Stop by anytime you'd like.
好极了  那就这么定了
Wonderful! Then it's settled.
我明天一大早就去拜访你们
I'll see you at your house, first thing tomorrow.
提前说声不用谢  回见
You're welcome in advance! Ta!
那女人似乎精神错乱
That woman seems deranged.
她的脸让我想到一张死亡面具
Her face reminds me of a death mask.
"精神错乱"  "死亡面具"
"Deranged"? "Death mask"?
你告诉我她有口臭
You tell me she's got halitosis,
我就娶定她了
and I'm hearing wedding bells!
帕格斯利  这是亚当斯家族的马刀
Pugsley, this is the Addams family saber.
三百年来亚当斯族人
300 years of Addams
都手持这把马刀跳玛祖卡舞
have danced the Mazurka with this blade.
你要先做好准备
Only when you've shown me you're ready.
你父亲是亚当斯家族最伟大的武士
Your father was the greatest swordsman in Addams history.
他的玛祖卡舞堪称传奇
His Mazurka was the stuff of legends.
所以别有压力
So no pressure!
都在这里  这本玛祖卡舞手册中
It's all right here, in the Mazurka handbook.
每个亚当斯都通过这个仪式
Every Addams performs this rite of passage
证明自己做好了捍卫家庭的准备
to show that you're prepared to defend your family.
听起来简单  但相信我  其实特别难
It sounds easy, but believe me, it's insane!
费斯特  给他那把咕咕嘎嘎婴儿训练用刀
Fester, hand him the goo-goo-ga-ga baby training sword.
爸爸
Pop?
有人没学会玛祖卡舞吗
Has anyone ever failed the Mazurka?
有一次  你三代堂兄山德
Once. Your third cousin, Xander.
从没听过他
Never heard of him.
那就对了
Exactly.
音乐
Music!
门口有人
There's someone at the door.
大家好  我要进这座诡异的房子
Hi, guys. I'm going up to this creepy mansion.
直播
如果三十分钟后没有消息  派人来支援
If you don't hear from me in 30 minutes, send backup.
你按了门铃吗
You rang?
好吧  不行
Yeah, no.
生命太短暂  再见
Life's too short. See ya!
早上好  基蒂
Good morning, Kitty.
你好  尼德勒女士
Greetings, Ms. Needler.
早上好  希望我没有打扰你们
Good morning! I hope this isn't a bad time.
打扰到了  请进
The worst. Do come in.
格伦
Glenn?
欢迎来到这里
Welcome to the neighborhood.
谢谢
Thank you.
老天
Oh, my!
准备好迎接玛尔戈大改装了吗
Are you ready for your Margaux makeover?
录制
相当
Quite.
帕格斯利期待得一直爬墙
Pugsley's been climbing the walls in anticipation.
不错不错
Well, well, well!
我们四处看看吧
Let's take a look around, shall we?
你们什么也别说  不客气
And before you say anything, you're welcome.
如果想让这里更加现代
Now, if we're trying for a more contemporary look,
这些壁式烛台必须去掉
well, these sconces have to go.
壁式烛台是死去亲人送的礼物
The sconces were a gift from dead relatives.
如果去掉它们
If we get rid of them,
他们下次来会很伤心的
they'll be terribly hurt the next time they visit.
这是我们的牢骚窖
And this is our whine cellar.
和"酒窖"谐音
我们收藏的牢骚特别棒
We have a lovely collection of whines.
-还没到吗  -我要冰淇淋
- Are we there yet? - I want ice cream!
你说牛油果吐司没了是什么意思
What do you mean you're out of avocado toast?
这桶让我显得肥
This barrel makes me look fat.
这是我们的无底洞
And here's our bottomless pit.
我们怎么穿过去
How do we get across?
等一下
One moment.
我们称这为"网上冲浪"
We call this surfing the web.
好吧
Well!
我害怕
I'm scared.
我好害怕
I'm so scared.
天啊
Oh, my gosh.
我害怕闭上眼
I'm scared to close my eyes.
我害怕睁开眼
I'm scared to open them.
那么多人是怎么塞进这个小装置的
How do all those people fit in that little contraption?
我的化妆镜一次只能囚禁十四个灵魂
My vanity mirror only imprisons 14 souls at a time.
你没有手机吗
You don't have a cell phone?
真奇怪
That's weird.
我或许没有手机
I may not have a cell phone...
你也没有弩
Well, you don't have a crossbow,
我还以为大家都有呢
and I thought everybody had one of those.
我叫星期三
My name is Wednesday.
好吧
Okay.
我是派克  你在这里住多久了
I'm Parker. How long have you lived here?
我这一生  感觉十分漫长
My whole life. Which seems endless.
我在学校从没见过你
I've never seen you at school.
我在笼子里上学
I'm cage-schooled.
-什么  -超级无趣
- Excuse me? - It's terribly dull,
但我妈妈坚持那样
but my mother insists.
其实我现在要脱笼了
I'm actually cutting cage right now.
好吧
Okay.
你的学校都有什么
So, what happens at your school?
没什么  就朋友反目
Not much, just friends turning on each other.
一些女孩让另一些女孩感到自卑
Girls making other girls feel bad about themselves.
典型的初中生活
Typical junior high stuff.
有趣
Intriguing.
人人都能去你们学校吗
Can anyone go to your school?
我想是的  但谁会想去
I guess so. But who'd want to?
星期三
Wednesday!
准头不错
Great shot!
亚当斯先生和太太
Mr. and Mrs. Addams,
把这里变得完美要做的并不多
there's really not much to do to make this place perfect.
我们只需拆掉侧墙
All we have to do is pull down the side walls,
还要拆除其他两面墙
and then also break down the other two walls.
不可逆地拆除天花板
Open up the ceiling by breaking it irreversibly.
把这讨厌的地板弄走
Just get this nasty little floor out of the way,
就好了
and there you go.
只需这些变动...
With just those little touches...
停下  不许动
Stop! Right there!
什么也不要碰
Don't touch another thing!
真是完美  尼德勒女士  你真有天赋
It's perfect. Ms. Needler, you have a gift.
好消息是我能叫装修队
The good news is I can have a makeover crew up here
明天一早就来这里动工
and swinging hammers first thing in the morning.
你们觉得呢
What do you say?
我们以为你改完了
We thought you were finished.
我们整个家族两周后要来
Our whole family is coming in two weeks.
我们的大结局
Our finale!
我们的大结局也在两周后
Our finale is in two weeks.
谢谢你  格伦
Thank you, Glenn.
尼德勒女士  你的好意我们心领了
It's a gracious offer, Ms. Needler,
但你做的已经够多了
but you really have done enough.
我们儿子要跳玛祖卡舞  你应该理解
It's our son's Mazurka. You understand.
谢谢
Thank you.
米奇不见了
We're missing Mitch.
他在哪
Where's Mitch?
出去
Get out!
米奇是谁
Mitch who?
戈麦斯  我直说了
Gomez, I'll be blunt.
下面那小区我有五十栋房子要卖
I have 50 houses to sell down there,
从那里看到你的房子
and their view of your property is, well,
有点掉价
off-brand.
-五十栋房子  -是的
- Fifty houses? - Yes.
自从我的家族
You know, ever since my family
从故乡被赶出来
was chased out from the old country,
我唯一的梦想就是
my one dream has been
找到一个能称为家的地方
to find a place we could call home.
一旦他们看到同化镇
Once they see Assimilation,
他们应该会想要永远留下
I think they'll want to stay for good.
非常感谢你前来  玛目布伦
Thank you so much for coming by, Membrane.
我叫玛尔戈
It's Margaux!
那好  逃吧  玛尔戈
Well then, run, Margaux!
跑  跑  跑
Run, run, run!
那个叫星期三的女孩是怪胎
That Wednesday girl is a freak.
我们即将被一大群怪胎入侵
We're about to be invaded by a whole army of freaks.
总有人接受不了自己急需帮助  真是可悲
It's tragic when people can't accept the help they so badly need.
出现这种情况
And when that happens,
就需要另一种介入了
well, another kind of intervention is called for.
我同意  戈麦斯
I agree, Gomez.
整个家族搬来这里会是美梦成真
The whole family moving here would be a dream come true.
但我不相信那个叫玛尔戈的
But I don't trust that Margaux woman.
她是个怪人  亲爱的  给她个机会
She's an eccentric, darling, give her a chance.
"覆盆子果酱"
"Rasp-berry preserves."
肯定是某种芳香防腐剂
Must be some kind of scented embalming fluid.
星期三  别找你父亲练习潜伏了
Wednesday, practice your lurking on someone other than your father.
一点挑战都没有
He's too easy.
好多了
Much better.
母亲  父亲  我想和你们谈谈
Mother, Father, I'd like to speak with you.
你想说什么  我的小夜行者
What's on your mind, my little nightcrawler?
我下午和派克聊天了
I spoke with Parker this afternoon.
她是今天来的那个活体模型的女儿
She's the daughter of that talking mannequin who came by.
她跟我说了一个公立学校
She told me about a communal school
附近所有小孩都去那里上学
all the neighborhood children attend.
叫什么"初中"
It's called "Junior high."
"初中"
"Junior high"...
对了  我在异常心理学期刊上
Yes, yes, I have read about those
读到过
in my abnormal psycholog journals.
任何适龄的小孩都能入学
Anyone of age can enroll.
我觉得这对我有好处
I think it would be good for me.
我认为这是个很好的主意
Well, I think it's a capital idea.
那你在家里的学习怎么办
What of your studies here?
你的标本剥制术进步非常大
Your taxidermy is coming along so well.
母亲  你真的要剥夺我
Mother, would you really deprive me
折磨同龄人的机会吗
of the opportunity to torment children my own age?
她说得有道理
Ah, she makes a point.
而且  星期三去上学了
What's more, with Wednesday in school,
我们就能更好地了解这里的人
we'd get to know the people here even better.
怎么样  母亲
Well, Mother?
同化中学
祝你上学愉快  宝贝
Have a good day at school, dear.
好好搞破坏
Do your worst!
我明白了  这是间少年监狱
Ah. Now I understand. This is a children's prison.
那是谁
Who's that?
真"棒"
Great.
这位是星期三
This is Wednesday.
你们好
Hello.
派克
Hey, Parker.
有好东西给你
I got something for ya.
一个发霉的三明治
A moldy sandwich?
你退步了  贝瑟妮
You're slipping, Bethany.
你知道吗  你说对了
You know what? You're right.
我们再加点料
Let's kick it up a notch.
你真是一点幽默感都没有
You have no sense of humor!
-你看她那张脸  -就是
- Did you see her face? - I know.
你叫贝瑟妮是吗
Bethany, is it?
除非你想和我结梁子  否则别惹我的人
Don't cut your eyes on my crew unless you're ready to dance.
你说什么  小僵尸
What did you say, little ghoul?
不要忘记给候选人投票
我想你没搞明白
I don't think you understand.
并非是我被困在你这里  贝瑟妮
I'm not locked up in here with you, Bethany.
而是你被困在我这里了
You're locked up in here with me.
随便吧
Whatever.
你做了什么
What did you do?
你不该和她那么说的
You shouldn't have said that.
你什么都做不了  贝瑟妮比你受欢迎多了
There's nothing you can do. Bethany's way too popular.
热度都是转瞬即逝的
Popularity is fleeting.
我更想把自己的目光
I prefer to set my sights
放在更有挑战性的事情上
on something a little more challenging.
比如什么
Like what?
确立威望
The establishment.
我想想  今天穿哪件"马甲"发帖呢
Let's see. Who shall I be today?
《设计干预》粉丝主页  简易图纸  可爱膝上狗
不如
How about...
邻居之窥  尼德勒个人主页
住在糖桥巷的雪莉·朗巴顿
Ah, Shelly Longbottom, on Sugar Ridge Lane.
雪莉·朗巴顿发送给所有人
From Shelly Longbottom to everyone,
邻居之窥
"你们听说了
"Did you hear
那一家叫亚当斯的人吗"  问号
about those Addams people?" Question mark.
"我听说他们在三十个州被通缉"
"Someone told me they're wanted in 30 states."
发送
你知道吗  他们花园里种植着食人植物
You know they're raising a garden of man-eating plants?
还把我们的宠物喂给它们吃
And feeding them our pets!
有人看见我的西施犬飞飞了吗
Has anyone seen my Shih Tzu Fee-fee?
他们会把我们全都变成僵尸
They're gonna turn us all into zombies.
他们到底是从哪来的
Where are they from anyways?
那无关紧要
It doesn't matter!
反正他们不属于这
It's obvious they don't belong here.
亲爱的  那些住在山顶的坏人
Honey! Oh, those awful people up on the hill.
他们甚至都不上"邻居之窥"
They're not even on Neighborhood Peeps!
那太可疑了
Well, that's suspicious.
如果其他人害怕了  那我也害怕了
If other people are scared, then I'm scared.
我相信网上读到的一切
I believe everything I read.
如果有人在网上发帖了
If someone posted it,
那绝对是真的
it must be true.
让一家怪人住进来  所有怪人都会来
You invite one family in, then all the families come in.
你觉得我们该不该调查一下
Do you think we should investigate?
我怕得脸都白了
I'm turning grey.
我为孩子们担忧
I'm worried for the children!
我们得和玛尔戈谈谈
We need to talk to Margaux!
我听说他们训练动物来偷我们的孩子
他们连邻居之窥APP都不用
把书翻到第43页
Open your books. Page 43.
按照说明操作
Follow the instructions.
恶心
Yuck.
我干过几千次了
I've done this thousands of times.
合闸
Flip the switch!
赐予这生灵生命吧
Give my creature life!
活过来  活过来  我命令你  复活
Live! Live, I tell you, live!
青蛙活了  它活过来了
It's alive! It's alive!
我的天  我的老天  把它们弄走
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Get them off me!
僵尸青蛙
Zombie frogs!
贝瑟妮换造型了
Bethany's changed her look.
这很适合她
It suits her.
太棒了  这简直太棒了
Awesome. Totally awesome.
能看到你
It is an honor...
大显身手
...and a privilege...
是我们的荣幸
...to watch you work.
你想去逛商场吗
Hey. Do you wanna go to the mall?
为什么不呢  我好久没见过像样的大扫荡了
Why not? I haven't seen a good mauling in ages.
很晚了  我很担心
It's late. I'm worried.
亲爱的  星期三不会有事的
Darling, Wednesday will be fine.
她能照顾好自己
She can take care of herself.
我担心的不是星期三
It's not Wednesday I'm worried about.
而是其他人  我们可能需要提供不在场证明
It's the rest of them. We may need to provide an alibi.
我的爱  今晚是游戏之夜
My love, it's game night.
星期三很快就会回来了
Wednesday will be home soon,
你何不来和我们一起玩
so why don't you come and join us?
好吧  F-6
Oh, very well. F-6.
帕格斯利  你听到你母亲的话了
Pugsley, you heard your mother.
炸掉F-6
Blow F-6!
开火
Fire in the hole!
我是世界之王
I'm king of the world!
♪ 无论远近  不管你身在... ♪
♪ Near, far, wherever... ♪
成功
Yes!
你把我的战船炸沉了
You sunk my battleship.
干得漂亮  帕格斯利
Ha-ha! Well done, Pugsley!
你们好  我的丑孩子们
Hello, my uglies!
母亲  怪不得刚才起鸡皮疙瘩了
Mother! I thought I felt my skin crawling!
孩子他奶奶  这太让人惊喜了
Grandma, what a surprise.
我以为你在布拉格
I thought you were in Prague.
我之前是在布拉格
I was!
他们抓到我从动物园偷鳄鱼
They caught me smuggling crocodiles out of the zoo.
不过我逃掉了
But I escaped and talked my way
然后靠耍嘴皮子上了索马里海盗船
onto a Somali pirate ship.
我们玩了一局激烈的扑克
We got into a heated poker game
我把的他们钱全赢回来了
and I cleaned them out.
-出老千还是抢劫  -二者兼有
- Cheating or robbery? - Both!
帕格斯利  永远记住
Always remember, Pugsley,
如果没人逮到你  就不算出千
it ain't cheating if no one catches you.
我都俩礼拜没洗澡了
I haven't bathed in two weeks. Ugh.
也许是两个月
Or is it months?
我想起来了
Ha! That reminds me.
猜猜我带了什么  帕格斯利
Guess what I've got, Pugsley?
-糖果  -太棒了
- Candy! - Oh, yes!
玛祖卡舞仪式还要一周才开始
But the Mazurka isn't for a week.
你怎么这么早来了
Why are you here so early?
戈麦斯说你需要人帮你准备派对
Gomez said you needed a little help with the party.
我想  我为我的儿子备战了玛祖卡舞
And I said, I got my son ready for his Mazurka,
那当然我也会为我的孙子出力
so of course, I'm going to do the same for my grandson.
我爱他
I love him!
确实如此  我让她来的
It's true! I sent for her!
我难以相信
I can't believe you bothered
你用这事麻烦你母亲  亲爱的
your mother with that, darling.
我也不太相信
Neither can I?
他说你脑袋都晕了
He said you were in over your head.
我谢谢您了  母亲
Thank you, Mother!
说他从未见过你这么紧张
Said you were more tense than he's ever seen you.
-我才没有那么说  -你说了
- I didn't say that exactly. - Yes, you did.
你原话就是那么说的
You said that exactly.
他说很担心你会极度不悦  然后
Said he was worried you'd have a massive facial expression and...
行了  我饿了  我们吃饭吧
You know, I'm starving! Let's eat!
星期三回来了才能吃
Not until Wednesday gets home.
我孙女呢
Where is that granddaughter of mine?
我给她带东西了
I got something for her!
我的小风暴回来了
Ah, there's my little storm cloud!
星期三  你去哪了
Wednesday, where have you been?
去外面了
Elsewhere.
你戴的是什么
What are you wearing?
派克把它叫做一点提亮的点缀
Parker calls it a pop of color.
我还挺喜欢这匹
While I certainly appreciate a horse
头上插着矛的马
with a spear through its head,
但这颜色...
the color is...
她说这和我的笑容很相称
She claims it brings out my smile.
星期三  你不会笑
Wednesday, you don't have a smile.
看起来有很多关于我的事情
Turns out I have a lot of things
你不知道
you don't know about.
看来我来得很及时
I see I got here just in time.
你给我打电话是对的  戈麦斯
You were right to call, Gomez.
我会和她谈谈  把那个猎熊陷阱递给我
I'll talk to her. Hand me that bear trap.
谢谢你  奶奶  不过我会处理这事的
Thank you, Grandma. But I will handle this.
随你便吧
Ah, suit yourself.
当你们不需要法比奥了  让他去我房间
When you're done with Fabio, send him up to my room.
我的天
Oh, boy!
星期三
Wednesday.
明天你放学之后要不要和我一起
How would you like to join me tomorrow
去墓地参加通灵茶话会呢
after the school for tea and séance in the cemetery?
是强制出席吗
Is attendance mandatory?
别这样  我的小乌鸦
Come now, my little raven.
你小时候特别喜欢的
You did so love it when you were younger.
你想去就去吧  母亲
If you like, Mother.
睡个好觉  宝贝
Sleep well, dear.
别忘了踢你父亲一脚道晚安
Don't forget to kick your father good night.
少年粉红泡泡  赢得他的心
你最喜欢的滤镜是哪个
What's your favorite filter?
我不知道
I don't know.
不管用什么滤镜我看起来都是黑白的
I look black and white in all of them.
你知道吗  我刚认识你的时候
You know, when I met you,
我觉得你特别奇怪
I thought you were super weird.
而现在  我觉得你超级酷
But now, I think you're really cool.
我同意
I concur.
你也不是全无优点
You're not completely devoid of merit yourself.
我该说谢谢吗
I wanna say "Thank you"...
派克·尼德勒
你昨天戴着哪个发夹回家
Oh, how'd that barrette
反响如何
you bought yesterday go over at home?
事实上  我母亲的反应有点反常
Actually, my mother's reaction was, well, unexpected.
她在试图接受  这让我很压抑
She was accepting. It depressed me.
没人想看见自己的母亲那样
One never wants to see one's mother that way.
但我不得不承认
But I must admit,
戴着那种鲜艳怪异的东西走来走去
walking around in something so garish, so grotesque...
没想到我还挺激动的
I was shocked how thrilling it felt.
我希望我也能那么做
I wish I could do that.
但我妈非要我穿这个
But my mom makes me wear this stuff,
这太...
and it's just so...
你想说的应该是"不幸"
I believe the word you're looking for is "Unfortunate."
我非常想疯狂一把
Ugh. I'd love to just go crazy
穿一些会让她震惊的服饰
and wear something that would shock her.
那么  派克
Well, Parker,
你很幸运
you're in luck.
你正巧在同惊悚女王说话
You happen to be talking to the queen of shock.
是
你好  妈妈
Hello, Mother.
我的小幽灵在哪里
Where's my little wraith?
星期三还没到呢
Wednesday still hasn't arrived.
我们说好来这里进行通灵茶话会
We agreed to come up here for tea and séance,
但现在她放了我鸽子
and now it seems she stood me up.
莫蒂西亚  你听得到吗
Morticia! Can you hear me?
你的做法不对
You're not doing it right.
-按那个按钮  -我按了  按了
- Press that button there. - I did! I did!
你听到按键咔嗒的声音了吗
Did you hear it click?
莫蒂西亚
Morticia!
你听到咔嗒声
It's supposed to be on
-应该就打通了  -等等  我看到了
- when you hear the click. - Wait, I see something.
你成功了  你好  亲爱的
You did it! Hello, darling!
我的外孙女在哪里
Now, where's my granddaughter?
正如我刚刚所说
Just what I said.
我认为她正在有意疏远我
I think she's distancing herself from me.
她被充斥着空虚与渴望的
Oh, she's wrapped in a black hole
黑洞所包裹
of emptiness and longing,
我们弗朗普家的女人都这样
like all of us Frump women.
-星期三  -不是星期三
- Wednesday? - It's not Wednesday!
-那是谁  -是我  爸爸
- Who's this? - It's me, Father.
莫蒂西亚
Morticia?
你怎么了
What's wrong with you now?
世界如此残酷
The world can be so cruel.
而她却只想直奔其而去
And all she wants to do is run toward it.
她那方面很像你
She's a lot like you that way.
你也曾想见识外界
You wanted to see the world.
探寻自我  风水轮流转
Find yourself. Serve time!
莫蒂西亚  你还记得那次
Listen, Morticia, remember the time
你跑去参加女童子军吗
you ran away and joined the Girl Scouts?
我们当时特别担心你走上歪路
We were so worried you were on a bad path.
但等你发现篝火是用来烤棉花糖
But when you found out that campfires
而不是烤其他女童子军时
were for roasting marshmallows and not other Girl Scouts,
你感觉无聊  就回家了
well, you got bored and you came home.
我们大大松了一口气
We were so relieved.
相信星期三
Trust Wednesday.
她会像你一样做正确的事
Like you, she'll do the right thing.
谢谢你  爸爸  我很受安慰
Thank you, Father. That's most comforting.
好  等等
Good. Wait a second.
我什么时候死的
When did I die?
二十年前
20 years ago.
好  纪念日快乐  亲爱的
Oh, right. Happy anniversary, darling.
好了  帕格斯利  我们再演练一遍
All right, Pugsley, let's, uh, go through it again.
喝掉这个  帕格斯利  玛祖卡不值一提
You got this, Pugsley. This Mazurka's nothing.
你能把刀剑当早饭吃
You eat swords for breakfast.
你就是有一点临场紧张
You just got a case of pre-ball jitters.
很多人都会这样
It's way more common than you think.
如果玛祖卡持续时间超过四小时
If a Mazurka lasts for more than four hours,
联系你的医生
contact your doctor.
从头来  音乐
From the top. Music!
帕格斯利
Pugsley,
我可以坦白讲
I can honestly say
你刚刚跳得确实很有特色的
that was most definitely a thing you did.
有一个问题  那到底是什么舞
A question, what in heaven's name was it?
马刀玛祖卡舞
The Sabre Mazurka.
你练习得很刻苦
You know what? You've been practicing hard.
今天何不到此为止呢
Why don't we call it a day?
去洗澡  孩子
Hit the showers, kid.
我们练完了
So, we're finished?
对
Ah, yes.
对  儿子  我们绝对练完了
Yes, son. We are most certainly finished.
好  谢谢  爸
Okay. Thanks, Pop.
谢谢  费斯特叔叔
Thanks, Uncle Fester.
简直是彻头彻尾的灾难  怎么会这样
This is a complete disaster! How did this happen?
他会自取其辱的
And he's going to make a fool of himself
当着所有人的面
in front of everyone!
戈麦斯  你得冷静
Gomez, you gotta calm down!
还有一天时间可以让他准备
There's still a day to get him ready!
费斯特  一年都不够他准备的
Fester, a year wouldn't be enough to get him ready.
我辜负了他  费斯特
I've failed him, Fester.
我努力把他培养成一亚当斯  但我失败了
I tried to raise him to be an Addams, but I failed.
他们会把他生吞活剥的
They're going to eat him alive.
♪ 我喜欢那样  宝贝 ♪
♪ I like it like that. Ooh, baby ♪
♪ 我说我喜欢那样 ♪
♪ I said I like it like that ♪
♪ 宝贝  我喜欢那样 ♪
♪ Ooh, baby, I like it like that ♪
好  谢谢
All right. Thank you.
奶奶  我们已经有一支乐队了
Grandma, we already have a band.
他们是太平间强烈推荐的
They came highly recommended from the mortuary.
他们当然不错
I'm sure they're good.
我姐姐思露会负责评判帕格斯利
My sister Sloom is going to be judging Pugsley.
如果不按照传统行事
And if things aren't done the traditional way,
她会不高兴
she won't be happy,
然后玛祖卡仪式会变成一场灾难
and the Mazurka could be a disaster!
但我又知道什么呢
But what do I know?
行
Fine.
我们拿下演唱会了
Yay, we got the gig!
我们拿下了
We got it!
还有一件事
Ah, one more thing...
有人敲门  我最好去看看是谁
Oh, someone's at the door. I'd better go see who it is.
♪ 当你可以泯然众人 ♪
♪ What's so great about being yourself ♪
♪ 又何必做你自己 ♪
♪ When you can be like everyone else? ♪
不许那么对你妈妈说话
Do not speak to your mother that way.
你怎么敢这样进家门
How dare you enter this house like that.
你的文身呢
Wait, where are your tattoos?
感谢星辰
Oh, thank the stars!
-你去哪了  -和派克一起玩
- Where were you? - Hanging out with Parker.
所以你才没来通灵茶话会吗
Is this why you skipped tea and séance?
你外祖父母想和你联系
Your grandparents were trying to contact you.
伟大的哈迪斯
Holy Hades!
无论这是谁对你做的  星期三
Whoever did that to you, Wednesday,
我希望他比你更难看
I hope the other guy looks worse.
没人对我这么做  这是我的新形象
Nobody did this to me. This is my new look.
你喜欢吗
Do you like it?
我不喜欢
I do not like it.
人人都知道粉色是入门色
Everyone knows pink is a gateway color.
你送她去公立学校时  我警告过你
I warned you about sending her to public school.
别担心
Don't worry.
星期三永远不会去那上学了
Wednesday is never going to that school again.
-什么  -事实上
- What? - In fact,
她再也不会离开这房子了
she's never leaving this house again.
她眼神真邪恶
Wow, that's some evil eye she's got there.
那种死亡凝视是新学的
No, that dead-eye stare is new.
我想我知道她从哪里学的
And I think I know where she got it.
大家好  是我
Hey, guys, this is me now.
如果你喜欢  请点击"喜欢"
If you like it, hit "Like,"
但谁在乎你喜不喜欢呢
but who cares if you like it.
我要活出真实的自我
I'm living my truth.
派克
Parker?
-这是谁干的  -我
- Who did this to you? - I did.
这是我的新形象  妈妈
This is my new look, Mother.
从现在起  我自己选衣服穿  你别管
I decided that from now on, I choose my clothes, not you.
都是那个古怪的星期三·亚当斯干的好事
This is that little creep Wednesday Addams' work!
她不古怪  她只是不像你一样
She's not a creep. She's just not like you.
你为什么不能容忍别人和你不一样
Why can't you ever let people be different?
因为让人人都一样是我的使命
Because it's my calling to make everyone the same.
太亮了  烧到我了
Too bright! It burns!
好  说不定能把你身上的古怪烧掉呢
Good! Maybe it'll burn away the weird!
我讨厌这里
I hate it here!
人人都虚假无趣而明亮
Everything's boring and fake and bright,
仿佛塑料花
like plastic flowers!
仿佛你
Like you!
派克  塑料花永远不会开败
Parker! Plastic flowers live forever.
你回房间去好好反省一下
Now, you go think about that in your room.
不许上社交软件
With no social media.
不  求你  不要  什么都行  就是别这样
No! Please, no. Anything but that!
快去把你脸上这阴沉玩意擦掉
Now go wipe that depressing goop off your face.
你先
You first!
姓亚当斯的这次太过分了
Those Addamses have gone too far this time.
他们需要一点小小的帮助
I think they're going to need a little more help.
同化镇
邻居之窥
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
一个朋友家
A friend's.
我囚禁其他人  而非他人囚禁我
I hold people prisoner, not the other way around.
祝你玛祖卡日好运
Good luck with your Mazurka.
等等  你要走了
Wait, you're leaving?
那谁来每天折磨我
Who's gonna torment me every day?
住在这屋檐下就够你受罪的了
Living under this roof is all the torment you'll need.
另外  我们的父母已经说得很明白
Besides, our parents have made it clear
只有和他们保持一致
that the only way to be accepted in this family
才能被这家庭接纳
is to be exactly like them.
我无法再遵守这些规则了
I can't play by those rules anymore.
再见  帕格斯利弟弟
Farewell, brother Pugsley.
明天  你会成为一个男人
Tomorrow, you become a man.
我则会成为一名逃犯
And I become a fugitive.
早就知道会变成这样
Always kinda knew it'd end up like this.
就是没想到会这么快
Just didn't think it'd be so soon.
我永远都不会忘记你的  帕格斯利
I'll never forget you, Pugsley!
但我会尝试忘记
But I'll try.
帕格斯利  看到你姐姐了吗
Pugsley, have you seen your sister?
她不在她房间
She's not in her room.
帕格斯利  星期三在哪里
Pugsley. Where's Wednesday?
滴答滴答  妈妈
Tick, tock, tick, tock, Mother.
你感觉很困
You're getting very sleepy.
帕格斯利
Pugsley...
她没去她朋友家
She did not go to her friend's house.
她去她朋友家了
She went to her friend's house?
我重复  她没去她朋友...
I repeat, she did not go to her friend's...
Everybody Hurts - R.E.M.
♪ 白昼漫长 ♪
♪ When the day is long ♪
♪ 而夜晚 ♪
♪ And the night ♪
♪ 独属于你一人 ♪
♪ The night is yours alone ♪
♪ 当你确信这种人生 ♪
♪ When you're sure - you've had enough - ♪
♪ 已经忍无可忍 ♪
♪ of this life ♪
♪ 请等等 ♪
♪ Hang on ♪
♪ 别轻易放弃 ♪
♪ Don't let yourself go ♪
♪ 因为人人都会哭泣 ♪
♪ 'Cause everybody cries ♪
无悔
♪ 人人都会伤心 ♪
♪ And everybody hurts ♪
♪ 有时候 ♪
♪ Sometimes ♪
我会和你一起住一阵
I shall be staying with you for a while.
♪ 人人都会伤心 ♪
♪ Everybody hurts ♪
如果失败
If this doesn't work,
我们卖的下一座房子就要算到你头上
the next house we flip is gonna land on you.
马蒂  听我说
Marty, listen to me.
明天  我们的最终集将是你们台
Tomorrow, our finale will be the biggest half hour
收视率最高的半小时
your network has ever aired.
只有一件事要搞定
There's just one more thing to take care of.
最好如此  否则你以后
This better be good or you won't be able
连当门垫的资格都没有了
to get a job as a doormat.
好好好
Yes, yes, yes.
我要拆掉那座房子
I intend to bring the house down.
堂亲
Drop It Like It's Hot
- Pharrell Williams
♪ When the pimp's in the crib ma ♪
♪ Drop it like it's hot. Drop it like it's hot ♪
♪ Drop it like it's hot ♪
♪ When the pigs try to get at you ♪
♪ Park it like it's hot. Park it like it's hot ♪
♪ Park it like it's hot ♪
♪ And if a... get a attitude ♪
♪ Pop it like it's hot. Pop it like it's hot ♪
♪ Pop it like it's hot ♪
♪ I got the Rolly on my arm and I'm pouring Chandon ♪
♪ And I roll the best... 'cause I got it going on ♪
你按的门铃
You rang?
是它  表妹  你终于来了
It. Cousin. You made it!
请进  别拘束
Please, come in. Make yourself at home.
她把我的手机藏哪去了
Where did she hide my phone?
我差不多有三天
I haven't been able
没发午餐照片了
to post a photo of my lunch in almost three days!
那里面呢
And what about in there?
那是我妈妈的工作室
That's my mom's crafting room.
谁都不可以进去
No one is allowed in there.
那肯定就在里面
Then that's where it is.
好诡异
Weird.
藏得够深的
Hidden depths.
这是什么
What is this?
汉尼先生在做三明治
There's Mr. Haney making a sandwich.
那个家伙要给他的猫穿迷你燕尾服
And that guy trying to put a tiny tuxedo on his cat.
-坐着别动  -那是弗林先生
- Sit still! - That's Mr. Flynn.
你怎么这么难搞
Why are you being so difficult?
-想让你看起来帅一点  -我赌猫赢
- Trying to make you look handsome. - My money's on the cat.
这是我们的科学老师  格雷夫利夫人
And there's our science teacher, Ms. Gravely,
她把内衣放在冰箱里
putting her underwear in the freezer?
我妈妈肯定在所有房子里
My mom must have built hidden cameras
都装了隐形摄像头
into all of the houses.
她真是变态
She really is psycho.
-派克  -天啊
- Parker! - Whoa!
妈妈
Hey, Mom.
我们到处找你
We were just looking for you.
我的工作室  我怎么跟你说的
What have I told you about Mommy's crafting room?
对不起  但是规矩是用来遵守的
Sorry to do this, but standards must be upheld.
派克  有一天你会明白的  星期三
Parker, someday you'll understand, and, Wednesday...
就这样了  派克
Well, anyway, Parker.
我妈妈有暗室还有牢房
My mom has a lair and a jail?
早该选择跟我爸过的
I knew I should have picked to live with my dad.
我们要上电视了
We're gonna be on TV!
我们会出名吗
Are we gonna be famous?
格伦  你要怎么拍
Glenn, what do you want in the frame?
好了  大家听好了
Okay, everyone, listen up.
这是结束前最后一次排练
It's the last run-through before the finale,
我们最后再过一遍  好吧
so let's try this one last time, okay?
我们从镇广场拍到眺望台
We're gonna shoot across the town square to the gazebo
玛尔戈会在那里隆重登场
where Margaux will make her grand entrance.
所以大家都往这个方向走
So everyone will be walking this direction
穿过广场
across the square.
朱迪  你从这里开始
Judy, you start here,
肯  你跟着朱迪
Ken, you're gonna follow Judy.
你就站在这里
You can stand right here and...
这附近有厕所吗
Uh, is there a bathroom nearby?
玛尔戈  他们来了
Margaux, they're here!
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
他们来了
They're here!
亚当斯一家
The Addams family!
请原谅
Pardon me.
对不起
Excuse me.
我们怎么办
What are we gonna do?
我们一贯的做法  格伦  帮助大家
What we always do, Glenn. Help people.
"亚当斯一家子怪人计划
"The Addams monsters are planning
今晚袭击本镇"
to attack the town tonight!"
感叹号
Exclamation point.
"现在到玛尔戈家碰面"
"Meet at Margaux's house now."
向你们表以敬意  亚当斯  我们来了
Salutations, Addams. We're here!
佩妮  我很喜欢你的发型
Petunia, I love what you've done with your hair.
谢谢  我刚叫人修的
Thanks, I just had it mowed.
请进  拘束点
Please, come in. Make yourself uncomfortable.
洋葱叔叔
Uncle Onion!
好久不见
It's been so long!
是啊  见到你太失望了
Yes, so disappointed to see you.
你总能让我感动到哭
You always manage to bring a tear to my eye!
你好  法兰布医生  最近怎么样
Greetings, Dr. Flambe! How you doing?
-我火烧头顶了  -太好了
- I'm on fire! - Good!
这个派对会燃起来的
This party's gonna be lit!
思露姨妈
Auntie Sloom.
Auntie Sloom!
你就像桶核废料一样魅力四射
You are as radiant as a barrel of nuclear waste.
你儿子呢
Where is the boy?
帕格斯利
Pugsley?
在那
There you are.
下来跟思露姨妈问好
Come down and say hello to your Auntie Sloom.
戈麦斯  这项传统可不能随便糊弄
Gomez, this tradition is not to be taken lightly.
我相信你儿子已经接受过正规训练
I trust that the boy has been properly trained.
是的  等你看完我们...
Yes, once you see how we've...
在新泽西举办仪式已经就够糟糕的了
It's bad enough this Mazurka is taking place in New Jersey.
渣滓在哪  我渴了
Now, where are the dregs? I'm thirsty.
你们见过他们
You've seen them!
也在邻居之窥上听说过他们的故事
You've heard the stories on Neighborhood Peeps!
亚当斯一家不是人  他们是魔鬼
Those Addams aren't people, they're monsters!
现在  他们入侵我们的生活
And now, there's an infestation of them!
他们会摧毁我们美丽的家园
They're here to destroy our beautiful community
把我们的家变成《设计干预》都法挽救的地方
and turn it into a place that no Design Intervention can save!
这里不欢迎亚当斯一家
Addams aren't wanted here!
他们是魔鬼  全都是魔鬼
They're monsters! They're all monsters!
我们要先下手为强  消灭他们
We need to destroy them first!
谁跟我一起
Who's with me?
一个小时之后我们会将同化镇
We'll be revealing Assimilation
和你们大家转播给观众
and all of you to our audience in just an hour.
帮助他们的最后时机就是现在
Our last chance to help these people is now.
比尔  约翰  你们那可爱的投石车还在吗
Bill, John, do you still have that lovely catapult?
是的  还在
Yes, we do!
你确定吗
Are you sure about this?
我们不能让他们毁了我们的家园
We can't let them ruin our neighborhood!
我们行动吧
Let's do it!
我要赶走他们
I want them out!
只有我能折磨我的家人
No one torments my family but me.
请把发夹给我
Hair clip, please.
好
Okay.
玛尔戈设计干预
笼子学校入门
Cage school 101.
最好他准备好了
He'd better be ready
否则思露姨妈会要了他的脑袋
or Auntie Sloom will have his head!
他看起来好小
He looks very small.
那孩子有苦头吃了
That kid's got some big shoes to fill.
真希望他准备好了
I certainly hope the boy's ready.
我不会对他手下留情的
Well, I'm not going easy on him.
头扔起来
Heads up.
女低音  你唱低了
Alto, you're flat.
思露
Sloom.
-姐姐  -亲爱的 我
- Sister. - Darling, I...
我知道上一次见面
I know the last time we saw each other,
我们吵得太凶了
we had that horrible fight.
我就想告诉你  真心地告诉你
And I just wanted to tell you, from the bottom of my heart,
那次我吵赢了  还好我是作弊赢的
I won that fight! And I was glad I cheated!
你赢了  你还是输不起  永远都是
You won? Still a sore loser, as always!
我们再比一次  就在这里  现在就比
I want a rematch! Right here! Right now!
思露姨妈  你要不要吃点东西
Auntie Sloom? Can I get you anything?
玛祖卡什么时候开始
When's the Mazurka?
快了  快了
Soon, soon.
我女儿星期三还没回来
Our daughter Wednesday isn't here yet.
如果你女儿赶不上
If your daughter can't be on time,
那我们就直接开始吧
then we will begin without her!
非常好  思露姨妈
Very well, Auntie Sloom.
请注意  请注意
Attention, please. Attention!
时间到了
The hour is upon us.
大家就位
Places!
我们今天聚集在这里  一起见证我儿子
We gather today to witness my son,
帕格斯利·亚当斯
Pugsley Addams,
表演马刀玛祖卡舞
perform his Sabre Mazurka.
他先读《恐怖》的一个章节
He will begin with a reading from the Terror,
以纪念我们在战斗中的呐喊
which commemorates our cries in battle.
咆哮
尖叫
现在是成年礼
And now, the transition into manhood.
胡须
现在是马刀玛祖卡舞
And now, the Sabre Mazurka.
别动
Hold still.
这是亚当斯胡须
The Addams mustache.
现在你准备好了
Now you're ready.
帕格斯利
Pugsley?
我放弃
I give up.
我做不到  爸爸
I can't do it, Pop.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我让你失望了
I let you down.
你没有让我失望  帕格斯利
You haven't let me down, Pugsley.
是我让你失望了
I let you down.
我如此沉迷于传统
I was so focused on doing things the traditional way,
忘记了让你做自己
I forgot to let you be who you are.
准备好迎接玛尔戈大改造了吗
Are ya ready for your Margaux makeover now?
是玛尔戈
It's Margaux.
她肯定把全镇的人
She must have turned the whole town
都教唆成彻头彻尾的疯子了
into stark raving lunatics.
不得不承认  她工作很出色
Well, I have to admit, I admire her work.
动手吧
Let's do this thing!
投石车装好了  玛尔戈
It's locked and loaded, Margaux.
干掉他们  我们受够了
Let's go get 'em! We've had enough!
发射
Fire!
滚出去
Get out!
帕格斯利
Pugsley!
玛祖卡的真正意义是什么
What is the true meaning of the Mazurka?
是保护我们的家人
It's about protecting our family
不受敌人的伤害
from those who would do us harm!
去吧  让他们瞧瞧你的绝技
Go ahead. Show 'em what you're good at.
我们要做的就是推倒四周的墙
All we have to do is pull down the side walls!
My Family - Migos, Karol G,
Snoop Dogg & Rock Mafia
♪ You shouldn't mess with me ♪
♪ You don't wanna mess with me ♪
♪ 'Cause if you mess with me you're messing with my family ♪
大家跟着我儿子走
Everyone, follow my boy!
大家好
Hey, guys!
♪ You might think that we are all loco ♪
♪ But this family is about to go global ♪
发射
Fire!
沙卡拉卡爆炸  宝贝
Shakalaka bang, baby!
快  这里出去
Quick! Out this way!
爸爸  我没有弹药了
Pop, I'm out of ammo!
我们被困住了
We're trapped!
希望我没扫大家的兴
Hope I'm not crashing the party.
星期三
Wednesday!
太好了
Yeah!
伊卡博德  快点  放下树枝
Ichabod, quick, lower your branches!
大家抓住了
Everyone, grab on!
项目没完成
Margaux Needler never stops
玛尔戈·尼德勒是不会停手的
until the project is complete.
小心手雷
Fire in the hole!
玛祖卡
Mazurka!
大家都还好吗
Is everyone all right?
你们来之前没缺的胳膊腿儿都在吧
No limbs missing that weren't missing before you arrived?
我的小乌鸦  很高兴你回来了
My little raven, I'm so happy you returned.
我当然会回来
Of course I came back.
我早知道
I knew there was no way
你们救不了自己
you were going to save yourselves.
你们就像虚弱的松鼠宝宝
You are like weak baby squirrels.
苏格拉底
Socrates.
八条腿  九条命
Eight legs, nine lives.
你说的没错
You were right, cara mia.
人们很残忍
People can be cruel.
我们干了什么
What have we done?
他们只是一家人
They're just a family.
一家人
A family?
别说笑了  他们就是一群怪物
Please! They're a bunch of monsters!
别在这时候心软  各位
Don't go soft on me, people.
我会驱赶你到天涯海角
I will relish hounding you
直到那座核废料场一般的房子
until that nuclear waste dump of a house is gone
和你那变态的一家都消失
and your mutant family along with it!
别轻易许愿  尼德勒女士
Be careful what you wish for, Ms. Needler.
我的家人和我再也不会躲避你这样的人了
My family and I will never run from the likes of you again.
深呼吸  玛尔戈
Deep breath, Margaux.
好了  我还要去拍大结局
Okay, I have a finale to shoot.
派克  我们走
Parker, let's go.
我不会跟你走的
I'm not going anywhere with you.
我要和朋友在一起
I'm staying with my friend.
你的朋友
Your friend?
派克  这些人是怪胎
Parker, these people are freaks.
如果他们是怪胎  那我也是
If they're freaks, then I'm a freak.
而且你们都是
And so are all of you.
证据A
Exhibit A.
格雷夫利女士  你把内衣裤放在冰柜里
Ms. Gravely, you put your underwear in the freezer.
那样很神清气爽  好吗
It's refreshing, okay?
证据B  特鲁迪·皮克林
Exhibit B. Trudy Pickering.
你反坐在马桶上
You sit on the toilet backwards.
不然我的手臂放哪儿呢
Well, where else am I supposed to put my arms?
等等  你怎么知道这些
Wait, how did you know that?
因为你们的房子都被尼德勒眼入侵了
Because your houses have been infested with Needler-Vision.
她在所有地方都装了隐藏摄像机
She has hidden cameras everywhere.
-什么  -并且一直监视着你们
- What? - And watches you all of the time.
-在我的私密时间吗  -那真是变态
- In my private time? - That is creepy, actually.
-她还看见什么了  -这实在太过分了
- What else has she seen? - That is over the line!
全都闭嘴
Shut up!
听着  你们这群没主见的人  这是我的小镇
Listen, you lemmings! This is my town.
你们不过是一群多余的人
You are nothing but a bunch of extras.
我们要走下山坡  献上一场真人表演
We are going to march down that hill and do a live show.
我希望你们能够说服
I expect you to convince
观众里那群没脑子的拉丁苦工们
those brainless peons out there in the audience
这里是购置房屋的绝佳地方
that this is the perfect place to buy a house,
否则你们都要滚出这里
or none of you will be living here much longer.
-你们听见了吗  -其实  妈妈
- Do you hear me? - Actually, Mom,
所有人都听见了
everyone can hear you.
你一直在直播
You've been live this whole time.
现在有三百万人正看着你呢
Three million people are watching you right now.
而这次  是真正的你
The real you, for a change.
得了吧  我根本不在乎网民怎么想
Please, what do I care what a bunch of bloggers think?
-玛尔戈  -什么事
- Margaux? - What?
电视台来电话了
It's the network.
他们要取消你的真人秀
They're taking your show off the air.
什么
What?
不行  那我就破产了
No. I'll be... I'll be bankrupt.
谁会来买这些房子呢
Who will buy all these houses?
看好了  我的机会来了
Okay, watch this. Now's my chance.
不好意思  我刚放屁了
Excuse me, I just tooted.
另外
Furthermore,
我觉得我能帮你卖掉这些房子
I think I can help you get rid of those houses.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
亲爱的
Well, my dear,
你手里有一大堆急需出售的房子
you've got a bunch of houses you need to get rid of,
而我有一大堆需要安置的家人
and I've got a bunch of family I need to get rid of.
你们好
Hello?
打扰一下  我叫特鲁迪
Excuse me. I'm Trudy.
特鲁迪·皮克林  我们从没正式认识过
Trudy Pickering. We... We never officially met...
对  反坐马桶的女士
Yes. The toilet woman.
就是我
Right.
听着  请给我们一个弥补过去的机会
Listen, please, give us a chance to make it right.
我们可以开一个属于自己的设计干预会
Let us have our own design intervention.
母亲  我和这些人待过
Mother, I spent time with these people,
没错  他们很奇怪
and it is true, they are odd.
但我们不该
But we shouldn't judge them
因为他们的不同而妄下评断
just because they're different.
-祝你今天愉快  -原来你在这儿
- Have a wonderful day! - And there you are.
-再见  -谢谢  再见
- Bye-bye. - Thanks! Bye!
你们好
Well, hello there!
你好  邻居  你的新房子怎么样了
Howdy, neighbor. How's the new house?
我超满意  希望你们带了伞
I love it. I hope you brought your umbrellas.
你放了台风  真是个好主意
You put in a typhoon. What a great idea.
别忘了礼物篮子  小傻蛋
Don't forget the gift basket, silly.
对  看我这记性
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
我们有清香防腐剂
We got scented embalming fluid,
脚趾  牙齿  水果蛋糕
toes, teeth, a fruitcake,
捕鼠器  还有些干杏子
rat bait, got some dried apricots...
带他就像训练小狗一样  超可爱  但劳人心
He's like training a puppy, adorable but tiresome.
她就是我的梦中情人
She's the woman of my dreams!
她的口气就像婴儿的尿布一样宜人
Her breath is like a baby's diaper.
费斯特  别闹了
Fester, stop!
谁能想到我这样一个零分男
Who would have thought a guy like me, a total zero,
能够和你这样的零分女牵手成功呢
would have ended up with you, an also zero?
快进来吧
Well, do come in!
可疑房屋地产经纪
令人神往的阁楼
现在房子修好了  帕格斯利
Now, with the house rebuilt, Pugsley,
可以给你举办你应得的庆祝会了
we can throw you the celebration you deserve!
你是真正的亚当斯家的人
You are Addams through and through.
滚出去
Get out!
真好  鬼魂也回来了
How lovely. The spirit's home.
一切终于回归正常了
Finally, back to normal.
我们干得真棒
We did good.
你不说  我也不说
I won't tell anyone if you don't.
Addams Family Theme - HeathisHuman
♪ 他们可怕又古怪 ♪
♪ They're creepy and they're kooky ♪
♪ 神秘又吓人 ♪
♪ Mysterious and spooky ♪
♪ 他们让人浑身发毛 ♪
♪ They're altogether ooky ♪
♪ 这就是亚当斯一家 ♪
♪ The Addams family ♪
♪ 他们的房子如同博物馆 ♪
♪ Their house is a museum ♪
♪ 人们好奇前来看 ♪
♪ Where people come to see 'em ♪
♪ 他们真的很幽默 ♪
♪ They really are a scream ♪
♪ 这就是亚当斯一家 ♪
♪ The Addams family ♪
干净
Neat.
贴心
Sweet.
小巧
Petite.
♪ 拿好女巫的披肩 ♪
♪ So get a witch's shawl on ♪
♪ 骑上能飞的扫帚 ♪
♪ A broomstick you can crawl on ♪
♪ 我们要去拜访拜访 ♪
♪ We're gonna pay a call on ♪
♪ 亚当斯一家 ♪
♪ The Addams family ♪
My Family - Migos, Karol G,
Snoop Dogg & Rock Mafia
♪ Family, family ♪
♪ I'd go to war for my family ♪
♪ Ups and downs, wrong or right, it's family ♪
♪ They think that we crazy ♪
♪ They say that we crazy, can't handle it ♪
♪ My back on the wall ♪
♪ Who I'mma call, my family ♪
♪ We different, ♪
♪ we stick out wig out, bug out ♪
♪ Pop out, hop out go ♪
♪ Ball out, show out ♪
♪ A'ight, this a party ♪
♪ Let's not make a problem. No! ♪
♪ Why you looking at me like there's something, tell me ♪
♪ You should know it's not just me that you'll be rubbing ♪
♪ The wrong way, so you better think twice ♪
♪ You shouldn't mess with me ♪
♪ You don't want to mess with me ♪
♪ 'Cause if you mess with me ♪
♪ You're messing with my family ♪
♪ You shouldn't mess with me ♪
♪ You don't want to mess with me. No! ♪
♪ 'Cause if you mess with me ♪
♪ You're messing with my family ♪
♪ You might think that we are all loco ♪
♪ Don't mess with my family ♪
♪ But this family about to go global ♪
♪ We blowin' up! ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Don't mess with my family ♪
♪ A'ight, this a party. Let's not make a problem ♪
♪ No! Why you looking at me like there's something, tell me ♪
♪ You should know it's not just me ♪
♪ that you'll be rubbing the wrong way ♪
♪ So you better think twice ♪
♪ You shouldn't mess with me ♪
♪ You don't wanna mess with me ♪
♪ 'Cause if you mess with me ♪
♪ You're messing with my family ♪
♪ You shouldn't mess with me ♪
♪ You don't wanna mess with me ♪
♪ 'Cause if you mess with me, ♪
♪ you're messing with my family ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ You're messing with my family ♪
♪ Yeah Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Don't mess with my family. No! ♪
♪ You might think that we are all loco ♪
♪ But this family about to go global ♪
♪ They say that we mean (Mean) ♪
♪ They say that we rude (Rude) ♪
♪ They say we got problems (Problems) ♪
♪ But we say it's cool ♪
♪ Family, family ♪
♪ I'd go to war for my family ♪
♪ Ups and downs wrong or right, it's family ♪
♪ You might think that we are all loco ♪
♪ Don't mess with my family ♪
♪ But this family is about to go global ♪
Haunted Heart - Christina Aguilera
♪ There's no bell ♪
♪ When you call for me ♪
♪ You'll be falling for miles ♪
♪ I'm bewitched by your misery ♪
♪ But I love it when you smile ♪
♪ Let me know what you want from me ♪
♪ Whisper "love" in my ears ♪
♪ Before you try to get your hooks in me ♪
♪ I should warn you, my dear ♪
♪ My heart is a haunted house ♪
♪ Once you're in, you ain't getting out ♪
♪ It's the trap you've been waiting for ♪
♪ Ain't no windows, ain't no doors ♪
♪ No escaping the way you feel ♪
♪ It's like a dream, but you hope it's real ♪
♪ My, my, my heart ♪
♪ M-m-m-my heart is a haunted ♪
♪ Haunted house ♪
♪ watch yourself when you walk to me ♪
♪ Careful where your heart treads ♪
♪ Suddenly, you'll be in too deep ♪
♪ You'll be caught up in my web ♪
♪ You will think of me constantly ♪
♪ And it will drive you insane ♪
♪ Like the tattoo you can't remove ♪
♪ Like the blood in your veins ♪
♪ My heart is a haunted house ♪
♪ Once you're in, you ain't getting out ♪
♪ It's the trap you've been waiting for ♪
♪ Ain't no windows, ain't no doors ♪
♪ There's no escaping the way you feel ♪
♪ It's like a dream, but you hope it's real ♪
♪ My, my, my heart ♪
♪ M-m-m-my heart is a haunted (Haunted) house ♪
♪ It's a haunted house (Haunted house) ♪